Jaydatt Champavat

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ENGINEER · FULLSTACK DEVELOPER 141/2, Sector-28, Gandhinagar 382028, Gujarat, India

、 (+91) 960-100-7303 | ■ jaydattc@gmail.com | ★ https://jaydattc.github.io/ | 🖸 jaydattc | 🛅 jaydattc

Summary_

Currently a freelance web developer. 2+ years of experience specializing in web development and infrastructure automation utilizing industry forefront tools such as **ReactJS**, **GraphQL**, **GatsbyJS**, etc. Adept in React workflows with several state management libraries (**Redux**, **XState**, **Recoil**, etc). Interested in delivering better and creative methods of problem-solving for challenging tasks, and keen to explore and learn new technologies and tools.

Work Experience _____

Slick Technologies Pvt. Ltd.

Remote - Ahmedabad, Guiarat

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT INTERN

Jul. 2020 - current

- Created stable and maintainable codebases with performant and accessible React components.
- · Creating features, functionalities and extending capabilities of a ERP Single Page Application built in React, MaterialUI, Redux and Redux Saga.
- Worked briefly on Shopify eCommerce using Liquid, JQuery and JSON.

Samaj Infotech Gandhinagar, Gujarat

JR. NODEJS DEVELOPER

Jul. 2019 - Nov. 2019

• Implemented a RESTful API server and an ERP Single Page Application for a management system consisting of product manufacturing management, Inventory management, Accounting, User Authorisation and Invoice generation in MERN stack.

Honors & Awards

2018 27th Rank, CodeChef API Hackacthon 2018

Ahmedabad, India

2018 **Regionals Qualifiers**, Gujarat Industrial Hackathon 2018

Ahmedabad, Ind

Projects _____

bDownload

GITHUB REPO

- A batch downloader cli made in NodeJS.
- Download using HTTP or curl (default is curl), Output folder selection, Batch downloading (downloading multiple files with serialized file names)

rhythmix

⊙ GITHUB REPO

- A polyrhythm trainer and tester for musicians made in ReactJS.
- · Listen to and practice to different polyrhythms or custom polyrhythms.

Education

Silver Oak University

Ahmedabad, India

B.E. IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

2017 - 2021

• 7.85 CGPA (till 6th semester)

Kendriya Vidyalaya No. 1

Gandhinaaar, India

12TH GRADE/HIGH SCHOOL

2017

• 86%